orangecountyscu.org 2019-01-13

# FACTS

Rev. 01/2011
                         WHAT DOES Orang County’s Cr dit Union
   FACTS                 DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                         Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
   Why?                  consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also re uires us to tell you
                         how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                         carefully to understand what we do.
  What?                  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                         have with us. This information can include:
                         ■   Social Security number            ■   date of birth
                         ■   income                            ■   account balances
                         ■   payment history                   ■   credit history
  How?                   All fnancial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                         business. In the section below, we list the reasons fnancial companies can share their
                         members’ personal information; the reasons Orange County’s Credit Union chooses to share;
                         and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                Do s Orang County’s
  R asons w can shar your p rsonal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                  Cr dit Union shar ?
   For our v ryday busin ss purpos s–
   such as to process your transactions, maintain                          Yes                          No
   your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
   investigations, or report to credit bureaus
  For our mark ting purpos s–                                              Yes                          No
  to offer our products and services to you
                                                                           Yes                          No
  For joint marketing with other financial companies
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–                          No                     We don’t share
  information about your transactions and experiences
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–                           No                    We don’t share
  information about your creditworthiness
                                                                            No                    We don’t share
  For nonaffiliates to market to you
  To limit               ■    Call 888-354-6228–our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) or
  our sharing            ■    Visit us online: www.orangecountyscu.org or via email at eservices@orangecountyscu.org
                         Pl as not :
                         If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                         sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information
                         as described in this notice.
                         However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
                            Call 888-354-6228 or go to www.orangecountyscu.org
  Qu stions?

Page 2
 Who w ar
  Who is providing this notic ?                   Orange County’s Credit Union
 What w do
 How do s Orang County’s Cr dit                  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
 Union prot ct my p rsonal                       and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
 information?                                    These measures include computer safeguards and secured fles
                                                 and buildings.
 How do s Orang County’s Cr dit                   We collect your personal information, for example, when you
 Union coll ct my p rsonal                        ■  open an account             ■ use your debit card
 information?                                     ■  apply for a loan            ■ pay your bills through bill payment
                                                  ■  make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                                  We also collect your personal information from others such as credit
                                                  bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
  Why can’t I limit all sharing?                  Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                  ■  sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes–information
                                                     about your creditworthiness
                                                  ■  affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                  ■  sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                  State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                  limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
 What happens when I limit sharing                Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
 for an account I hold jointly with
 someone else?
 D fnitions
 Affiliat s                                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                  fnancial and nonfnancial companies.
                                                  ■  Orange County’s Credit Union does not share with our affliate
                                                     Orange County Group Inc.
 Nonaffiliat s                                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                  fnancial and nonfnancial companies.
                                                  ■  Orange County’s Credit Union does not share with nonaffliates so
                                                     they can market to you.
 Joint mark ting                                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated fnancial companies that
                                                  together market fnancial products or services to you.
                                                  ■   Our joint marketing includes credit card companies and mortgage
                                                      servicing companies.
 Oth r important information
 In California, under the provisions of the California Financial Information Privacy (also known as SB-1), we need to
 provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of sharing with our joint marketing partners and sharing certain
 information with our affiliates.
 The state re uirement varies from the federal government’s re uirements described above and is addressed in the
 state privacy notice.
